cdn77.com 2019-08-08

# Privacy Policy | CDN77.com

  * #### Information about our organization and web site

  * CDN77.com main activity is commercial software development, sales, service, and support. Our privacy policy covers CDN77.com and its web site (the "Site"), www.cdn77.com.

  * #### Providing visitors with anonymous access

  * You can access our web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.

  * #### The services and links of our web site

  * The Site does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others.

The Site may include links to third party Web service providers.

  * #### Automatic collection of non-personal information (visitors)

  * We may collect non-personal data when you visit our Site. For example, we collect data such as randomly assigned numeric identifiers with respect to general Site usage on a non-personally identifiable basis. Other non-personal data may be collected by our partners for statistical purposes. We use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. The data are processed in accordance with applicable laws, including the GDPR. We do so for the following purposes:

    * Statistical purposes
    * Marketing
    * Social media features

  * #### Automatic collection of personal information (customers and logged users)

  * We may automatically log personal data by means such as programming or we may link information automatically logged by such means with personal data about specific individuals. We may also use cookies to store personal data or we may link information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. The data are processed in accordance with applicable laws, including the GDPR. We do so for the following purposes:

    * Technical administration of the web site
    * Research and development
    * Customer administration
    * Marketing

  * #### Data collection and purpose specification

  * We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using the Site. We do not collect information about Site visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations. We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated at the point on the Site of collection. If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose by indicating in a box at the point on the Site where personal data is collected.

  * #### Children’s privacy

  * We do not knowingly collect personal data from or about children. Children are not eligible to use the Site, and they should not submit any personal information to us.

Additionally, to ensure that children's privacy is respected on the Site, we remove and destroy all information that may be collected about any child.

  * #### Disclosure and visitor choice

  * We disclose our visitors' personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations. Where we disclose your personal data for the same purposes as those indicated at the point on the Site where personal data is collected, we provide you with the means to opt-out of disclosure by indicating in a box at the point on the Site where personal data is collected.

Where we disclose your personal data for purposes which are different from those indicated at the point on the Site where personal data is collected, we offer you the opportunity to consent to disclosure by indicating in a box at the point on the Site where personal data is collected.

  * #### Confidentiality/security

  * We give you the option of using a secure transmission method to send us the following types of personal data:

    * Primary personal data (such as name and contact details)
    * Identifiers (such as credit card details, web site password)

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:

    * Unauthorized access
    * Improper use or disclosure
    * Unauthorized modification
    * Unlawful destruction or accidental loss

All of our employees and data processors who have access to, and are associated with, the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data.

Please note that personal data may be disclosed in compliance with legally mandated reporting and disclosure requirements, as well as judicial, subpoena, warrants, or other government orders and legal process requirements.

  * #### Access to the personal data we may hold about you

  * You can ask us, by sending an email (to [support@cdn77.com](mailto:support@cdn77.com)) whether we are keeping personal data about you.

Upon request, which you can indicate by sending an email (to [support@cdn77.com](mailto:support@cdn77.com)), we will provide you with a machine-readable, structured copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within 30 days. This requires proof of your identity. We verify email address associated with your request.

We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data:

    * Erased
    * Rectified or amended
    * Completed

We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data. We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.

  * #### Privacy support

  * If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact us at [support@cdn77.com](mailto:support@cdn77.com)
